<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="扩容" />
      <item value="the time unit for the {@code keepAliveTime} argument" />
      <item value="when the number of threads is greater than the core, this is the maximum time that excess idle threads will wait for new tasks before terminating." />
      <item value="Modification" />
      <item value="bubble" />
      <item value="concurrent" />
      <item value="Dummy value to associate with an Object in the backing Map" />
      <item value="Cancelled" />
      <item value="Indicates how often (in seconds) the eureka client needs to send heartbeats to eureka server to indicate that it is still alive. If the heartbeats are not received for the period specified in leaseExpirationDurationInSeconds, eureka server will remove the instance from its view, there by disallowing traffic to this instance. Note that the instance could still not take traffic if it implements HealthCheckCallback and then decides to make itself unavailable." />
      <item value="The largest possible table capacity. This value must be exactly 1&lt;&lt;30 to stay within Java array allocation and indexing bounds for power of two table sizes, and is further required because the top two bits of 32bit hash fields are used for control purposes." />
      <item value="CAPACITY" />
      <item value="transient" />
      <item value="This implementation iterates over &lt;tt&gt;entrySet()&lt;/tt&gt; searching for an entry with the specified value. If such an entry is found, &lt;tt&gt;true&lt;/tt&gt; is returned. If the iteration terminates without finding such an entry, &lt;tt&gt;false&lt;/tt&gt; is returned. Note that this implementation requires linear time in the size of the map." />
      <item value="Sole" />
      <item value="failure" />
      <item value="file Suffix" />
      <item value="CURRENT" />
      <item value="This can be the class name or a primitive. The value will override the data type as read from the class property." />
      <item value="primitive" />
      <item value="ensure Capacity" />
      <item value="The {@code String} class represents character strings. All string literals in Java programs, such as {@code &quot;abc&quot;}, are implemented as instances of this class. &lt;p&gt; Strings are constant; their values cannot be changed after they are created. String buffers support mutable strings. Because String objects are immutable they can be shared. For example:" />
      <item value="Handler" />
      <item value="Approximates Eureka zones from a host name. This method approximates the zone to be everything after the first &quot;.&quot; in the host name." />
      <item value="命令" />
      <item value="Past History" />
      <item value="surefire" />
      <item value="detected" />
      <item value="Annotation which indicates that a method parameter should be bound to a web request parameter. &lt;p&gt;Supported for annotated handler methods in Spring MVC and Spring WebFlux as follows: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;In Spring MVC, &quot;request parameters&quot; map to query parameters, form data, and parts in multipart requests. This is because the Servlet API combines query parameters and form data into a single map called &quot;parameters&quot;, and that includes automatic parsing of the request body. &lt;li&gt;In Spring WebFlux, &quot;request parameters&quot; map to query parameters only. To work with all 3, query, form data, and multipart data, you can use data binding to a command object annotated with {@link ModelAttribute}. &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;If the method parameter type is {@link Map} and a request parameter name is specified, then the request parameter value is converted to a {@link Map} assuming an appropriate conversion strategy is available. &lt;p&gt;If the method parameter is {@link java.util.Map Map&amp;lt;String, String&amp;gt;} or {@link org.springframework.util.MultiValueMap MultiValueMap&amp;lt;String, String&amp;gt;} and a parameter name is not specified, then the map parameter is populated with all request parameter names and values." />
      <item value="Performs a final update on the digest using the specified array of bytes, then completes the digest computation. That is, this method first calls {@link #update(byte[]) update(input)}, passing the &lt;i&gt;input&lt;/i&gt; array to the {@code update} method, then calls {@link #digest() digest()}." />
      <item value="digest" />
      <item value="Matrix" />
      <item value="failures" />
      <item value="You'll need to remove the spaces from the html entities below" />
      <item value="Annotation indicating a method parameter should be bound to the body of the web request. The body of the request is passed through an {@link HttpMessageConverter} to resolve the method argument depending on the content type of the request. Optionally, automatic validation can be applied by annotating the argument with {@code @Valid}. &lt;p&gt;Supported for annotated handler methods in Servlet environments." />
      <item value="病史" />
      <item value="慢性病" />
      <item value="Radiation" />
      <item value="原因" />
      <item value="treatment History Groups" />
      <item value="Custom Main Symptom Dectorator" />
      <item value="Retention" />
      <item value="注解" />
      <item value="Whether body content is required. &lt;p&gt;Default is {@code true}, leading to an exception thrown in case there is no body content. Switch this to {@code false} if you prefer {@code null} to be passed when the body content is {@code null}. @since 3.2" />
      <item value="Set the {@code value} and expiration {@code timeout} for {@code key}." />
      <item value="Overwrite parts of {@code key} starting at the specified {@code offset} with given {@code value}." />
      <item value="offset" />
      <item value="unit must not be" />
      <item value="url tname" />
      <item value="The unique id has 64bits (long), default allocated as blow:&lt;br&gt; &lt;li&gt;sign: The highest bit is 0 &lt;li&gt;delta seconds: The next 28 bits, represents delta seconds since a customer epoch(2016-05-20 00:00:00.000). Supports about 8.7 years until to 2024-11-20 21:24:16 &lt;li&gt;worker id: The next 22 bits, represents the worker's id which assigns based on database, max id is about 420W &lt;li&gt;sequence: The next 13 bits, represents a sequence within the same second, max for 8192/s&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt;" />
      <item value="Schedules the specified task for execution at the specified time. If the time is in the past, the task is scheduled for immediate execution." />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="110" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="110" />
        <entry key="DANISH" value="1" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="foldOriginal" value="true" />
    <option name="ignoreRegExp" value="\*" />
  </component>
</application>